Welcome friends, welcome to the IAS Law
Board results, the portfolio has a
very big meaning, almost got into fat, in these,
send a portfolio, there is a guitar activity
will, out of which there is boil, okay, 20
companies, service and away recently quit
Indian, so you Radhe Radhe Maa and this is that
today you are subscribing
to music, let me tell you an example weakness, the
₹1 company, the boxer, with one hand, with the
other hand, the biggest general
insurance company, go and do GICU
again in the roots,
their underwriting is
called reminder, okay, there is a command,
how much did you underwrite and I
took my cream of ₹100 for ₹100 and in the
case of ₹101, you mind, I
locked my ₹1 that I got injured, it was
plotted more than once, okay,
now like for a long time, I used to
live with the commander, 19, 108, seven, that
means on that  Lastly let's make a
reminder, as per the facility there used to be an
operating loss on the operating front, okay, but these
companies that were
general insurance companies, it will not be valid, come mind if you like
and comment small that we have double more
such crispy feel, the biggest
thing is that general insurance is the one that is
kept, okay, like gradually in that
manner subscribe to any channel,
definitely subscribe, subscribe, subscribe,
increase the dollar amount, that is the
thing that happens, it is half, sometime the
time will come that Bigg Boss is looking
for date, thank you, so how much money did he earn, okay,
rest let's see our result, everyone is
watching, definitely like this a little in Karuna,
I have Commander Suresh, it has decreased, it has
increased, that's why Vikas Job, till the last,
we had a lot of lukewarm glasses, that was quite a lot of
your underwriting, questions were little
school, the gene world loss remedy,
because what will happen now is that people used to make people eat the
last plate of rice, the
same amount of grinding is going to increase by 200 percent,
okay, okay, on this side it has definitely been
understood that something or the other will keep happening,
attacking health is  There is wealth
and here it seems that the other team will
not be needed Vikram Thakur, I had done
experience growing a plant e631 as to
what will be the sewerage connection, okay, we will see
one by one, we will see that, so
show the data of the sheds here,
I will have to break it down a little bit tomorrow morning, okay, so
again it is going to be a slide show from far
and wide open Bluetooth, tax of 25.25 to 2640 crores,
totally free, if you are buying a car,
subscribe and subscribe means
side 1st T20, if you have just seen the previous song
again,
quick commissioner 1984, okay,
when last this last scene, why we last year,
last few months, Bigg Boss, then
subscribe to this channel of yours from here, like or if it
happens, okay, then typing will happen,
mind mind people this year, total no,
win in their direction, amazing, low general
insurance, messages, silent chatting, it
is good for vitamin E, that 14th, okay, okay
and in this quarter, 10158 have
given the president,
come properly  There was profit and loss from licking the campaign district, it must be
innocent that it
definitely takes some time of capital, okay, it is difficult
for this, I had told that this is amazing,
subscribe to this thing, as many
subscribers as you want in our video, okay, okay then
subscribe, okay, okay,
this 368, think of big good
companies which have made a profit of 360 crores, this much has been made, then it has become a
sum,
and if you want to keep doing it, then stay for weeks, get more
trained, it is not against free, difficult for the general
insurance, it has
increased by 906,
that fat 23.4, how much famous, use the code 1473
and subscribe, you have to make 7276
profit, okay, this which has
helped now, if you subscribe, it
is good,
you will get a different everywhere, if you
have it, then it is fine, without saying anything,
people must be maintaining the
dream of increasing problems and returns from every age, it is
like varicocele, it is a company, anyone must
definitely subscribe, if you like, then
subscribe if you meet Mukherjee, it has happened
All these series page 7 Hari Career your 1.5 tab
okay so who is this person your shortage is very
tremendous ribbon in double you have double
silencer if today's shortage is fulfilled
properly return everything in place only then it is very
big so it seems that subscribe
thank you for watching my video
subscribe subscribe to my channel
thank you